// -------------------- Array for Questions --------------------

var questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT inlcude __________.",
        answerChoices: [
            "Strings",
            "Booleans",
            "Alerts",
            "Numbers"
        ]
        answer: "Alerts"
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "The condition in an if/else statement is enclosed with __________.",
        answerChoices: [
            "Quotes",
            "Parenthesis",
            "Curly Brackets",
            "Square Brackets"
        ]
        answer: "Parenthesis"
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store __________.",
        answerChoices: [
            "Numbers and Strings",
            "Booleans",
            "Other Arrays",
            "All of the Above"
        ]
        answer: "All of the Above"
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store __________.",
        answerChoices: [
            "Numbers and Strings",
            "Booleans",
            "Other Arrays",
            "All of the Above"
        ]
        answer: "D"
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "String values must be enclosed with __________ when being assigned to variables.",
        answerChoices: [
            "Commas",
            "Parenthesis",
            "Curly Brackets",
            "Quotes"
        ]
        answer: "Quotes"
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "A very useful tool during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is __________.",
        answerChoices: [
            "console.log",
            "JavaScript",
            "For Loops",
            "Terminal/Bash"
        ]
        answer: "console.log"
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "JavaScript is an __________ language.",
        answerChoices: [
            "Object-Based",
            "Object-Oriented",
            "Procedural",
            "All of the Above"
        ]
        answer: "Object-Based"
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: [
            "var",
            "let",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the Above"
        ]
        answer: "Both A and B"
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "When encountering empty statements, what does the JavaScript interpreter do?",
        answerChoices: [
            "Gives a Warning",
            "Ignores the Statement",
            "Throws an Error",
            "None of the Above"
        ]
        answer: "Ignores the Statement"
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "Which function is used to convert an object into a JSON string in JavaScript?",
        answerChoices: [
            "serialize()",
            "parse()",
            "stringify()",
            "convert()"
        ]
        answer: "stringify()"
    },
]